Why far pump-outs
cost more
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
if I publish my
prices
they're really
variable
right?
I have a lot
of people who
will have a
certain price
depending on the
distance from
their yard
it's wherever the
pump trucks live
overnight
But where do they
dump?
Where's their
dump site?
the price of
diesel is insane
And the wear and
tear on the
trucks and the
time it gets to
go to different
places
It really makes a
big difference
how far you go
out
especially with
pumping
with some of the
other services
like maintenance
or locating or if
you're doing like
an inspection or
an installation
you can afford to
go further
because the value
that you're
getting from
those services
quite a bit
higher than
pumping pumping
is quite a bit
lower it makes a
difference if
you're going 30
minutes away to
go pump
or if you're
going an hour and
15 minutes away